

PHILIP TOOLAN

CREATIVE CODER

PHILTOOLAN@GMAIL.COM

+353 838547623

PHILTOOLAN.WIXSITE.COM/WEBSITE

GITHUB.COM/PHILTOOLAN

ABOUT ME

I am a computer scientist specialising in real-time 3D and interactive programs. Creating something beautiful from just code excites me and working in this field is a dream job for me. The landscape is continuously evolving and I am motivated to continue learning and finding new ways to create impactful experiences.

EDUCATION

XAMK UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES

Introduction to Video Games Creation (25 ECTS) 2021 - Present

POLYGON RUNWAY

Become a 3D illustrator 2021

HOCHSCHULE DARMSTADT

European Double Degree in Information Technology 2019 - 2020

TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY DUBLIN

BSc. Computer Science (International) 2017 - 2021, First Class Honours

MARIST COLLEGE

Secondary School 2011 - 2017

EXPERIENCE

BASKETBALL COACH

Athlone Basketball Club & Basketball Ireland Academy 2014 - Present

FIXTURES SECRETARY

Athlone Basketball Club 2020 - Present



	English - Native Speaker			
	German - A2			
	French - B1			
	Irish - B2			
	PROGRAMMING I	LANGUAGES		
-		••••	CSS	••••
	Python	••••	Javascript	••••
	Java	••••		
	Prolog	••••	С	••••
	HTML	••••	SQL	••••
	SOFTWARE		_	
	Unity	••••	OpenCV	••••
	Blender	••••	Unreal	••••
	GitHub	••••	Photoshop	••••
	Jupyter	••••	InDesign	••••
	SOFT SKILLS		_	
	Communication	••••	Work Ethic	••••
	Teamwork	••••	Leadership	••••
	Positivity	••••	Critical Thinking	••••

LANGUAGES